Dhruvitkumar Patel

Student

Personal Info

- dhruvituk46@gmail.com
- 07901170285
- 492 Green street, Tuder Road, London E13 9DB, United Kingdom
- Indian
- **6** 05/09/2003

Education

- Bsc(hons) Data science & Artificial intelligence
 University of East London Jan 2023 - Present
- 12th | Higher secondaryEducation Board (65%)

Alembic Vidyalaya Jan 2020 - May 2021

Gujarat secondaryEducation Board (69%)

Alembic Vidyalaya Jan 2018 - Mar 2019

Core Skills

- Web Design Experienced
- Word Excel Experienced
- Microsoft Office Experienced
- · Python Beginner
- Teamwork Experienced
- Creativity Experienced

Summary

Passionate advertising professional experienced in planning and delivering high-performing marketing campaigns. Networks proactively to build tactical business and media relationships. Reaches target audience and achieves revenue goals through focused strategy and planning. Excellent problem-solving and analytical skills with attention to detail.

Work Experience

Delivery Driver, Just Eat (Part-Time), London

February 2023 - May 2023

- Safely and efficiently delivered food orders to customers doorsteps in a timely manner.
- Maintained a clean and well-maintained delivery vehicle.
 conducting regular inspections and reporting any issues.
- Communicated effectively with restaurant staff and just Eat's support team, providing updates and resolving issues collaboratively.
- Stayed up to date with relevant laws, regulations, and just Eat's policies and procedures.

Data Entry Clerk, office Beacon Private Ltd., Vadodara,India

June 2021 - September 2021

- Entering customer and account data from source documents within time limits.
- Compiling, verifying accuracy and sorting information to prepare source data for computer entry.
- Reviewing data for deficiencies or errors, correcting any incompatibilities, and checking output.

Computer Operator (Billing). Tilak Plywood & Hardware, Vadodara,India

November 2021-September 2022

- Managing some of warehouse products data.
- Document payment records and issues as they occur.
- Create billing and maintain client relation.